<translations>
    <language code="en">
        <string key="email">E-mail</string>
        <string key="password">Password</string>
        <string key="registrazione_successo">Data saved successfully.</string>
        <string key="registrazione_errore">An error has occurred while saving data: $e</string>
        <string key="titolo">Rome's guide for tourists</string>
        <string key="home_descrizione">Welcome, \nthis guide will allow you to discover the beauties of this city, orient yourself, and find the perfect itinerary for you based on your interests.\nWe will provide you with all the useful information that \nyou need to know before coming here, so that you can fully enjoy your experience!!</string>
        <string key="inizia_tour">Click here to take a tour of the attractions.</string>
        <string key="tasto_itinerario">Click here to choose the perfect itinerary for you</string>
        <string key="seleziona_lingua">Select Language</string>
        <string key="itinerario_1_gg">1 Day stay itinerary</string>
        <string key="itinerario_2_gg">2 days stay itinerary</string>
        <string key="itinerario_3_gg">3 days stay itinerary</string>
        <string key="itinerario_4_gg">4 days stay itinerary</string>
        <string key="scelta_itinerario">Choose your itinerary</string>
        <string key="tasto_mappa">Click here to view the map</string>
        <string key="inserisci_mail">Insert an e-mail</string>
        <string key="mail_valida">Insert a valid e-mail</string>
        <string key="inserisci_password">Inserire la password</string>
        <string key="password_valida">The password must contain at least 6 characters</string>
        <string key="nuovo_utente">Are you new?</string>
        <string key="registrati">Register!</string>
        <string key="singolo_giorno">Itinerary for 1 day</string>
        <string key="primo_giorno">First Day</string>
        <string key="secondo_giorno">Second Day</string>
        <string key="terzo_giorno">Third Day</string>
        <string key="quarto_giorno">Fourth Day</string>
        <string key="home">Home</string>
        <string key="preferiti">Favourites</string>
        <string key="meteo">Weather</string>
        <string key="mappa">Map</string>
        <string key="impostazioni">Settings</string>
        <string key="logout">Logout</string>
        <string key="altare_patria">L'altare della Patria</string>
        <string key="colosseo">Colosseo</string>
        <string key="fontana_trevi">Fontana di Trevi</string>
        <string key="piazza_popolo">Piazza del popolo</string>
        <string key="piazza_navona">Piazza Navona</string>
        <string key="san_pietro">San Pietro</string>
        <string key="piazza_spagna">Piazza di Spagna e la Barcaccia</string>
        <string key="fori_imperiali">Fori Imperiali</string>
        <string key="sant_angelo">Castel Sant'Angelo</string>
        <string key="via_corso">Via del corso</string>
        <string key="borghese">Villa Borghese</string>
        <string key="altare_patria_descrizione">The National Monument to Victor Emmanuel II, known as the Altare della Patria, is an Italian national monument located in Piazza Venezia. With its imposing size, boasting a height of 70 meters, the monument was officially inaugurated and opened to the public during the celebrations of the fiftieth anniversary of the Unification of Italy. It holds great symbolic value for the complex process of national unity and liberation from foreign domination achieved under the reign of Victor Emmanuel II of Savoy, to whom the monument is dedicated: for this reason, the Vittoriano is considered one of Italy's patriotic symbols. The monument also houses the Tomb of the Unknown Soldier, an Italian soldier who fell in battle during World War I. The Tomb of the Unknown Soldier is always guarded by two soldiers (positioned at the ends of the tomb) belonging to different branches of the Italian Armed Forces, who take turns in the service. You can visit the extensive Risorgimento Museum housed inside it and take the panoramic elevator to enjoy the view of Rome. For more information, visit the following link</string>
        <string key="sant_angelo_descrizione">Castel Sant'Angelo, also known as the Mausoleum of Hadrian, is a monument in Rome, located on the right bank of the Tiber River facing the Pons Aelius (now Ponte Sant'Angelo), not far from the Vatican. The statue of an angel crowning the building, from which it takes its name, is typical. Guided tours can be booked at the following link: </string>
        <string key="colosseo_descrizione">The Colosseum, originally known as the Flavian Amphitheater, is the largest Roman amphitheater in the world (capable of accommodating an estimated number of spectators between 50,000 and 87,000), located in the center of the city of Rome, as well as the most imposing monument of ancient Rome that has come down to us. Included in UNESCO's World Heritage List in 1980, it has also been included among the New Seven Wonders of the World. The amphitheater was built in the Flavian era on an area on the eastern edge of the Roman Forum. Its construction, started by Vespasian in 70 AD, was completed by Titus, who inaugurated it on April 21 in 80 AD. In ancient times, it was used for gladiator shows and other public events (such as animal hunts, naval battles, reenactments of famous battles, and dramas based on classical mythology). As of today, it is possible to make a reservation for a guided tour inside at the link provided below.</string>
        <string key="via_corso_descrizione">Via del Corso is a well-known historic street in the center of Rome that connects Piazza Venezia to Piazza del Popolo and measures approximately 1.6 kilometers. It is the central artery of the road complex known as the Trident. It is very famous for also being the shopping street, with numerous shops on both sides, all within walking distance of some of Rome's most important attractions. Highly recommended during the holiday seasons when it is adorned with themed decorative lights.</string>
        <string key="fontana_trevi_descrizione">The Trevi Fountain is the largest of Rome's famous fountains, built on the facade of Palazzo Poli by Nicola Salvi for the competition announced by Pope Clement XII in 1731. It is set in a large rectangular pool with rounded corners. The scenery is dominated by a rocky cliff that occupies the entire bottom part of the palace, at the center of which we find a large niche delimited by columns, making it stand out as if under a triumphal arch. Here stands a large statue of the god Ocean by Pietro Bracci, with muscular and opulent forms and a proud and haughty gaze. Symbol of the city it represents, and probably also the grandeur of the fountain itself, it has given rise to legends and anecdotes that have become part of Roman popular culture: The best-known and most persistent tradition is linked to the throwing of a coin into the fountain: by doing this act with closed eyes, facing away from Palazzo Poli, one would propitiate a future return to the city. It is possible to make a reservation for a guided tour where access to the underground spaces (nine meters deep) to see the 2000-year-old aqueduct is also available at the following link.</string>
        <string key="piazza_navona_descrizione">Piazza Navona is one of the most famous monumental squares in Rome. In ancient Rome, it was the Stadium of Domitian, built by the emperor in 85 AD. Entirely paved with cobblestones, it has a rectangular elongated shape and is adorned with three fountains and an obelisk. The particular geometry of the square is due to the previous circus that stood in its place during the Roman period. It is a symbol of Baroque Rome, with architectural and sculptural elements by Gian Lorenzo Bernini (such as the Fountain of the Four Rivers in the center of the square, representing the Danube, the Ganges, the Nile, and the Rio de la Plata, the four corners of the Earth), Francesco Borromini, and Girolamo Rainaldi (the church of Sant'Agnese in Agone, in front of Bernini's fountain). It also has two other fountains: the Fontana del Moro, sculpted by Giacomo della Porta and later modified by Bernini, located in the southern area of the square, and the Fontana del Nettuno (originally the Fountain of the Cauldron Makers), located in the northern area, a work by Gregorio Zappalà and Antonio Della Bitta.</string>
        <string key="fori_imperiali_descrizione">They constitute a series of five monumental squares built over a century and a half (between 46 BC and 113 AD) in the heart of the city of Rome by Julius Caesar and the emperors Augustus, Vespasian, Nerva, and Trajan. You can stroll along this historic street of Rome and observe open-air excavations and historical remains from that era. You can book a guided tour at the following link: </string>
        <string key="piazza_popolo_descrizione">Piazza del Popolo is one of the most famous squares in Rome, situated at the foot of the Pincio hill and serving as the meeting point of via del Babuino, via di Ripetta, and via del Corso, the three main arteries of Rome's historic center. At its center lies the Fountain of the Lions and it is surrounded by the Flaminio obelisk. It features round travertine basins, dominated by white marble lions in Egyptian style, from whose mouths water jets flow. In the center of the eastern hemicycle stands the Fountain of the Goddess Roma, adorned with a large sculptural group consisting of a statue of the armed goddess, flanked by two statues depicting the Tiber and the Aniene, the two rivers of Rome, with the she-wolf suckling the twins at their feet. Behind it lies the Pincio Park, a splendid urban promenade, from whose terrace one can admire a spectacular sunset. Exactly in the center of the opposite hemicycle rises the imposing sculptural group adorning the Fountain of Neptune: a statue of Neptune holding a trident in his right hand, with two tritons with dolphins at his feet. On the opposite side of the square stands the splendid fifteenth-century Basilica of Santa Maria del Popolo. Two twin churches were also built, Santa Maria in Montesanto, also known as the 'Church of the Artists', and Santa Maria dei Miracoli, designed in a completely symmetrical manner.</string>
        <string key="piazza_spagna_descrizione">Piazza di Spagna, at the foot of the monumental staircase of 136 steps that connects it to the church of Trinità dei Monti, is one of the most famous squares in Rome. It owes its name to the Spanish Embassy to the Holy See since 1622, which was formerly housed in the nearby Palazzo di Spagna. When viewed from above, it resembles the shape of "butterfly wings," formed by two triangles with a common vertex. At the center of the square stands the famous Barcaccia Fountain, dating back to the early Baroque period, created by Pietro Bernini and his son, the renowned Gian Lorenzo. On September 8, 1857, Pope Pius IX inaugurated the Column of the Immaculate Conception overlooking Piazza di Spagna in memory of the definition of the dogma of the Immaculate Conception. Currently, the floral tribute in Piazza di Spagna, always accompanied by a Marian prayer from the Pope, is one of the most beloved and popular religious ceremonies in Rome.</string>
        <string key="san_pietro_descrizione">The Papal Basilica of St. Peter in the Vatican, officially known as the Papal Basilica Major of St. Peter in the Vatican, is a Catholic basilica located in St. Peter's Square in the Vatican City State. It is a masterpiece of Italian art and one of the symbols of Rome, dominating the skyline with its dome. It is referred to as the largest church in the world both in terms of its dimensions and metaphorically for its importance as the center of Catholicism. It is also a UNESCO World Heritage Site known as the Vatican City, established in 1984. The arrangement of the square was created by Gian Lorenzo Bernini, with its oval shape and impressive colonnaded portico adorned with sculptures. St. Peter's Basilica boasts a length of 218 meters and a height up to the dome of 132.30 meters, with a total surface area of approximately 23,000 square meters and can accommodate 60,000 worshippers. The building is entirely accessible along its perimeter, providing access to the adjacent Vatican Museums, which are visited daily by thousands of tourists, especially for the famous Michelangelo frescoes in the Sistine Chapel. We recommend taking a guided tour to fully explore these spaces and be guided by a qualified guide. You can book a guided tour at the following link: </string>
        <string key="villa_borghese_descrizione">Villa Borghese is a large city park that includes various green areas, from Italian-style gardens to extensive English-style areas, buildings, small structures, fountains, and small lakes. You can stroll through the park, rent bicycles or rickshaws, take a boat ride on the characteristic lake, and enjoy the view of Rome from the famous Pincio Terrace overlooking Piazza del Popolo. It's a highly suitable attraction for families.</string>
        <string key="attrazioni_amate">Most loved attractions</string>
        <string key="apri_link">Open link</string>
        <string key="errore_link">Unable to open the link</string>
        <string key="temp_min">Min Temp</string>
        <string key="temp_max">Max Temp</string>
        <string key="vento">Wind Speed</string>
        <string key="umidità">Humidity</string>
    </language>
    <language code="it">
        <string key="email">E-mail</string>
        <string key="password">Password</string>
        <string key="registrazione_successo">Dati salvati con successo.</string>
        <string key="registrazione_errore">Si è verificato un errore durante il salvataggio dei dati: $e</string>
        <string key="titolo">Guida Turistica Roma</string>
        <string key="home_descrizione">Benvenuto, \nquesta guida ti permetterà di scoprire le bellezze di questa città, di orientarti e trovare l'itinerario perfetto per te in base ai tuoi interessi.\nTi daremo tutte le informazioni utili che \ndevi sapere prima di venire qui, in modo da goderti a pieno la tua esperienza!!</string>
        <string key="inizia_tour">Clicca qui per fare un tour della attrazioni</string>
        <string key="tasto_itinerario">Clicca qui per scegliere l'itinerario perfetto per te</string>
        <string key="seleziona_lingua">Seleziona Lingua</string>
        <string key="itinerario_1_gg">Itinerario per 1 giorno di permanenza</string>
        <string key="itinerario_2_gg">Itinerario per 2 giorni di permanenza</string>
        <string key="itinerario_3_gg">Itinerario per 3 giorni di permanenza</string>
        <string key="itinerario_4_gg">Itinerario per 4 giorni di permanenza</string>
        <string key="scelta_itinerario">Scegli il tuo itinerario</string>
        <string key="tasto_mappa">Clicca qui per consultare la mappa</string>
        <string key="inserisci_mail">Inserire una e-mail</string>
        <string key="mail_valida">Inserire una e-mail valida</string>
        <string key="inserisci_password">Inserire la password</string>
        <string key="password_valida">La password deve contenere almeno 6 caratteri</string>
        <string key="nuovo_utente">Sei nuovo?</string>
        <string key="registrati">Registrati!</string>
        <string key="singolo_giorno">ITINERARIO PER 1 GIORNO</string>
        <string key="primo_giorno">PRIMO GIORNO</string>
        <string key="secondo_giorno">SECONDO GIORNO</string>
        <string key="terzo_giorno">TERZO GIORNO</string>
        <string key="quarto_giorno">QUARTO GIORNO</string>
        <string key="home">Home</string>
        <string key="preferiti">Preferiti</string>
        <string key="meteo">Meteo</string>
        <string key="mappa">Mappa</string>
        <string key="impostazioni">Impostazioni</string>
        <string key="logout">Disconessione</string>
        <string key="altare_patria">L'altare della Patria</string>
        <string key="colosseo">Colosseo</string>
        <string key="fontana_trevi">Fontana di Trevi</string>
        <string key="piazza_popolo">Piazza del popolo</string>
        <string key="piazza_navona">Piazza Navona</string>
        <string key="san_pietro">San Pietro</string>
        <string key="piazza_spagna">Piazza di Spagna e la Barcaccia</string>
        <string key="fori_imperiali">Fori Imperiali</string>
        <string key="sant_angelo">Castel Sant'Angelo</string>
        <string key="via_corso">Via del corso</string>
        <string key="borghese">Villa Borghese</string>
        <string key="altare_patria_descrizione">Il Monumento nazionale a Vittorio Emanuele II , noto come Altare della Patria, è un monumento nazionale italiano situato a piazza Venezia. Con la sua imponente dimensione, vantando ben 70m di altezza, il monumento fu inaugurato ufficialmente ed aperto al pubblico in occasione delle celebrazioni del cinquantenario dell'Unità d'Italia. Ha un grande valore rappresentativo del complesso processo di unità nazionale e liberazione dalla dominazione straniera portato a compimento sotto il regno di Vittorio Emanuele II di Savoia, cui il monumento è dedicato: per tale motivo il Vittoriano è considerato uno dei simboli patri italiani. Il monumento accoglie anche la tomba del Milite Ignoto, militare italiano caduto al fronte durante la prima guerra mondiale. La tomba del Milite Ignoto è sempre piantonata da due militari (posizionati alle estremità della tomba) appartenenti alle diverse armi delle forze armate italiane che si alternano nel servizio. \nÈ possibile visitare l’ampio museo del Risorgimento custodito al suo interno nonché prendere l’ascensore panoramico e godersi la vista su Roma. Visita per maggiori informazioni il seguente link</string>
        <string key="sant_angelo_descrizione">Castel Sant'Angelo, detto anche mausoleo di Adriano, è un monumento di Roma, situato sulla sponda destra del Tevere di fronte al pons Aelius (attuale ponte Sant'Angelo), a poca distanza dal Vaticano. Tipica è la statua di un angelo che corona l'edificio, da cui prende il nome. Si possono effettuare visite guidate prenotabili al seguente link: </string>
        <string key="colosseo_descrizione">Il Colosseo, originariamente conosciuto come Anfiteatro Flavio è il più grande anfiteatro romano del mondo (in grado di contenere un numero di spettatori stimato tra 50 000 e 87 000), situato nel centro della città di Roma, nonché il più imponente monumento dell'antica Roma che sia giunto fino a noi. Inserito nel 1980 nella lista dei Patrimoni dell'umanità dell'UNESCO è stato anche inserito fra le Nuove sette meraviglie del mondo. L'anfiteatro fu edificato in epoca Flavia su un'area al limite orientale del Foro Romano. La sua costruzione, iniziata da Vespasiano nel 70 d.C., fu conclusa da Tito, che lo inaugurò il 21 aprile nell'80 d.C. Anticamente era usato per gli spettacoli dei gladiatori e altre manifestazioni pubbliche (spettacoli di caccia, battaglie navali, rievocazioni di battaglie famose e drammi basati sulla mitologia classica). \nAd oggi è possibile effettuare una prenotazione per una visita guidata al suo interno al link che ti forniamo qui sotto</string>
        <string key="via_corso_descrizione">Via del Corso è una nota strada storica del centro di Roma che collega piazza Venezia a piazza del Popolo e misura all'incirca 1,6 chilometri. È l'arteria centrale del complesso stradale conosciuto come Tridente. Molto famosa per essere anche la via dello shopping, presentando ambo i lati numerose proposte di negozi il tutto a pochi passi da alcune delle più importanti attrazioni di Roma. Molto consigliata nei periodi di festa dove viene abbellita con luci decorative a tema.</string>
        <string key="fontana_trevi_descrizione">La Fontana di Trevi è la più grande fra le celebri fontane di Roma, costruita sulla facciata di Palazzo Poli da Nicola Salvi, per il concorso indetto da papa Clemente XII nel 1731. È inserita in un'ampia piscina rettangolare dagli angoli arrotondati. La scenografia è dominata da una scogliera rocciosa che occupa tutta la parte inferiore del palazzo, al cui centro troviamo una grande nicchia delimitata da colonne che la fa risaltare come fosse sotto un arco di trionfo. Qui si erge una grande statua del dio Oceano di Pietro Bracci dalle forme muscolose e opulente e dallo sguardo fiero e altezzoso. Simbolo della città che rappresenta e probabilmente anche l'imponenza stessa della fontana è all'origine di leggende e aneddoti che le si infittiscono attorno e che sono entrati a far parte della cultura popolare romana: La tradizione più conosciuta e persistente è legata al lancio della monetina dentro la fontana: compiendo questo atto a occhi chiusi, voltando le spalle verso palazzo Poli, ci si propizierebbe un futuro ritorno nella città. È possibile effettuare una prenotazione per una visita guidata dove è possibile avere accesso anche agli ambienti sotterranei (ben nove metri) per vedere l'acquedotto di 2000 anni al seguente link</string>
        <string key="piazza_navona_descrizione">Piazza Navona è una delle più celebri piazze monumentali di Roma, ai tempi dell'antica Roma, era lo Stadio di Domiziano che fu fatto costruire dall'imperatore nell'85. Interamente rivestita in sampietrini, ha pianta di forma rettangolare allungata è dotata di tre fontane e di un obelisco. La particolare geometria della piazza è data dal precedente circo che sorgeva al suo posto in periodo romano.  È un simbolo della Roma barocca, con elementi architettonici e scultorei di Gian Lorenzo Bernini (la Fontana dei Quattro Fiumi al centro della piazza, che rappresenta il Danubio, il Gange, il Nilo ed il Rio della Plata, i quattro angoli della Terra), Francesco Borromini e Girolamo Rainaldi (la chiesa di Sant'Agnese in Agone, davanti alla fontana del Bernini). Ha anche altre due fontane: la Fontana del Moro, scolpita da Giacomo della Porta e ritoccata dal Bernini, situata nell'area sud della piazza, e la Fontana del Nettuno (originariamente fontana dei Calderari), situata nell'area nord, opera di Gregorio Zappalà e Antonio Della Bitta.</string>
        <string key="fori_imperiali_descrizione">Costituiscono una serie di cinque piazze monumentali edificate nel corso di un secolo e mezzo (tra il 46 a.C. e il 113 d.C.) nel cuore della città di Roma da parte di Giulio Cesare e degli imperatori Augusto, Vespasiano, Nerva e Traiano. È possibile passeggiare lungo questa via storica di Roma e osservare a cielo aperto gli scavi e i resti storici di quell’epoca. Si può prenotare una visita guidata al seguente link: </string>
        <string key="piazza_popolo_descrizione">Piazza del Popolo è una delle più celebri piazze di Roma, ai piedi del Pincio e al vertice in cui si incontrano via del Babuino, via di Ripetta e via del Corso, le tre arterie principali del centro storico di Roma. Al centro si trova la fontana dei Leoni e si sviluppa intorno all’obelisco Flaminio. Ha vasche rotonde di travertino, dominate da leoni di marmo bianco in stile egizio, dalle cui bocche sgorgano i getti d’acqua. Al centro dell’emiciclo orientale è collocata la fontana della Dea Roma, ornata da un grande gruppo scultoreo costituito da una statua della dea armata, affiancata da due statue raffiguranti il Tevere e l’Aniene, i due fiumi di Roma e ai cui piedi si trova la lupa che allatta i gemelli. Alle spalle, si trova il parco del Pincio, splendida passeggiata urbana, dalla cui terrazza si ammira un tramonto spettacolare. Esattamente al centro dell’emiciclo opposto, si erge l’imponente gruppo scultoreo che adorna la fontana del Nettuno: una statua di Nettuno con il tridente nella mano destra, ai cui piedi sono posti due tritoni con delfini Mentre sul lato opposto della piazza sorge la splendida Basilica di Santa Maria del Popolo di origine quattrocentesca. furono realizzate le due chiese gemelle, Santa Maria in Montesanto, nota anche come 'Chiesa degli Artisti', e Santa Maria dei Miracoli, progettate in maniera completamente simmetrica.</string>
        <string key="piazza_spagna_descrizione">Piazza di Spagna, ai piedi della monumentale scalinata di ben 136 gradini che la collega con la chiesa di Trinità dei Monti, è una delle più famose di Roma. Deve il suo nome al palazzo di Spagna, sede dell'ambasciata dello Stato iberico presso la Santa Sede dal 1622. Vista dall'alto appare come la forma ad “ali di farfalla”, formata da due triangoli con il vertice in comune. Al centro della piazza vi è la nota fontana della Barcaccia, che risale al primo periodo barocco, realizzata da Pietro Bernini e da suo figlio, il più celebre Gian Lorenzo. L'8 settembre 1857 Papa Pio IX inaugurò la Colonna dell'Immacolata che presiede Piazza di Spagna in ricordo della definizione del dogma dell'Immacolata. Attualmente l'omaggio floreale di piazza di Spagna, sempre accompagnato da una preghiera mariana del Papa, è una delle cerimonie religiose più amate e popolari di Roma.</string>
        <string key="san_pietro_descrizione">La basilica di San Pietro in Vaticano, ufficialmente papale basilica maggiore di San Pietro in Vaticano, è una basilica cattolica ubicata in Piazza San Pietro nello stato della Città del Vaticano; è un capolavoro dell'arte italiana e uno dei simboli di Roma, di cui domina il panorama con la sua cupola. È indicata come la più grande chiesa del mondo sia per le sue dimensioni sia, metaforicamente, per la sua importanza come centro del cattolicesimo, nonché Patrimonio dell'umanità UNESCO denominato Città del Vaticano e istituito nel 1984. La sistemazione della piazza fu realizzata da Gian Lorenzo Bernini, di forma ovale con l'imponente colonnato architravato sormontato da sculture. La basilica di San Pietro vanta una lunghezza di ben 218 metri e un’altezza fino alla cupola 132,30 metri, la superficie totale è di circa 23 000 metri quadrati e può contenere 60 000 fedeli. L'edificio è interamente percorribile lungo il suo perimetro, attraverso cui possiamo accedere anche agli adiacenti Musei Vaticani, i quali sono ogni giorno visitati ogni giorno da migliaia di turisti, in particolare per il famoso affresco di Michelangelo nella cappella Sistina. Vi suggeriamo di effettuare una visita guidata per poter esplorare al meglio questi ambienti e lasciarsi trasportare dalla spiegazione di una guida qualificata. Al seguente link: </string>
        <string key="villa_borghese_descrizione">Villa Borghese è un grande parco cittadino che comprende sistemazioni a verde di diverso tipo, dal giardino all'italiana alle ampie aree di stile inglese, edifici, piccoli fabbricati, fontane e laghetti. Potrete passeggiare per il parco, affittare bici o risciò, fare un giro in barca nel laghetto caratteristico e godersi la vista su Roma dalla celebre terrazza del Pincio che affaccia a picco su Piazza del Popolo. Attrazione molto adatta alle famiglie.</string>
        <string key="attrazioni_amate">Le attrazioni più amate</string>
        <string key="apri_link">Apri Link</string>
        <string key="errore_link">Impossibile aprire</string>
        <string key="temp_min">Temp Min</string>
        <string key="temp_max">Temp Max</string>
        <string key="vento">Vento</string>
        <string key="umidità">Umidità</string>
        <!-- Altre traduzioni per l'italiano -->
    </language>
</translations>
